Guide to the Joseph V. Charyk papers, 1957-1989 MS2137
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
Joseph V. Charyk papers
1957-1989
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
Charyk, Joseph Vincent
MS2137
44 Linear Feet
Collection contains correspondence, meeting minutes, speeches and addresses, calendars, legal documents, personnel files, exhibits, financial records, programs, brochures, photographs, and reports dating from 1957-1989 generated by Joseph Vincent Charyk during his time working for Communications Satellite Corporation (COMSAT).
Restrictions on Access
Some records may be restricted.
Acquisition Information
This collection was donated by COMSAT and Joseph Vincent Charyk in 1988.
Historical or Biographical Note
Joseph Vincent Charyk (1920- ) was a leader in the development of satellite technology. The son of Ukrainian immigrants, Charyk graduated from the University of Alberta, Canada in 1942 and received his Ph.D in Aeronautics from the California Institute of Technology in 1945. He spend time as an instructor at Princeton University, California Institute of Technology, and specifically at the Cal Tech Jet Propulsion Laboratory. He also worked for Lockheed Aircraft Corporation in the 1950s.
In 1963 in a move to the private sector, Charyk helped found and following incorporation became president and a director of Communications Satellite Corporation (COMSAT). In 1979, he was elected Chief Executive Officer and then served as Chairman of the Board of Directors from May 1983 until his retirement in October 1985. As Chief Executive Officer, Charyk was responsible for the overall management of the corporation and the chairmanship of the Board of Directors.
In 1973, Charyk was elected to the U.S. National Academy of Engineering in recognition of his contributions to space flight. The Intelsat system of commercial telecommunication satellites is used throughout the world.
The Communication Satellite Act of 1962 had as its goal to establish a world-wide commercial communications satellite system with the principal feature being a provision to establish a private corporation in the District of Columbia with the authority with foreign governments and business entities to plan and operate the communications satellite system. President Kennedy gave this charge to a group of appointed incorporators and they founded COMSAT.
Collection Scope and Content
This collection contains correspondence, meeting minutes, speeches and addresses, calendars, legal documents, personnel files, exhibits, financial records, programs, brochures, photographs, and reports. The material dates from 1957-89. These are the records of Joseph Vincent Charyk during his time working for Communications Satellite Corporation (COMSAT). Charyk served as Chief Executive Officer and later Chairman of the Board and the material in the collection covers how his work influenced the direction the company went related to satellite technology.
Collection Organization
Organized into five series: Administrative files; Organizations; Conferences, symposiums, and seminars; Correspondence; and Speeches.
Collection note
Please note: there are no boxes 65-70. These numbers were not used.
International Maritime Satellite Organization; Artificial satellites in telecommunication; Photographs; International Telecommunications Satellite Consortium; COMSAT Corporation; Communications Satellite Corporation; Charyk, Joseph Vincent
- Administrative files, 1962-1989; MS2137 Series 1; 29 Linear feet (Box 12, Box 11, Box 10, Box 9, Box 55, Box 35, Box 53, Box 54, Box 51, Box 52, Box 38, Box 50, Box 40, Box 39, Box 42, Box 41, Box 44, Box 43, Box 46, Box 45, Box 47, Box 48, Box 49, Box 58, Box 57, Box 56, Box 5, Box 6, Box 7, Box 8, Box 1, Box 2, Box 3, Box 4, Box 30, Box 31, Box 32, Box 33, Box 26, Box 27, Box 28, Box 29, Box 15, Box 16, Box 13, Box 14, Box 19, Box 20, Box 17, Box 18, Box 23, Box 24, Box 21, Box 22, Box 37, Box 36, Box 25, Box 34)
  Scope and Contents note
  This series contains correspondence, financial records, calendars, photographs, slides, personnel records, handbooks, and reports. The material dates from 1962-89. These records come from the work of Joseph Vincent Charyk while he was both Chief Executive Officer and Chairman of the Board of Communications Satellite Corporation (COMSAT). The records include both the internal workings of COMSAT and also how the company related to others in the satellite business.
  - ABM Material, 02/19/1969-03/20/1969 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    General note
  - Accounts Payable Internal Audit Report #80-1 February 22, 1980 Finance and Corporate Development, 02/22/1980-06/06/1980 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Administration 1969 [1/3], 04/03/1969-03/25/1970 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Administration 1969 [2/3], undated (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Administration 1969 [3/3], 02/14/1969-10/07/1969 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Administration, 02/28/1972-11/20/1973 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Advisory Council of the Center of Canadian Studies - SAIS, 04/07/1982-02/20/1985 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Aeronautical Satellite 1970-1974 [1/3], 07/19/1971-06/07/1974 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Aeronautical Satellite 1970-1974 [2/3], 07/24/1970-03/19/1971 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Aeronautical Satellite 1970-1974 [3/3], 02/02/1970-06/09/1970 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Aerospace Education Foundation, 04/07/1964-03/03/1966 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Algeria, 09/1973-12/29/1973 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Applicants - 1980 Personnel Administration, 02/22/1980-12/23/1980 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Appointments 1963, 01/01/1963-12/31/1963 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Appointments 1964, 01/01/1964-12/31/1964 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Appointments 1965, 01/01/1965-12/31/1965 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Appointments 1966, 01/01/1966-12/31/1966 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Appointments 1967, 01/01/1967-12/31/1967 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Appointments 1968, 01/01/1968-12/31/1968 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Appointments 1969, 01/01/1969-12/31/1969 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Appointments 1970, 01/01/1970-12/31/1970 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Appointments 1971, 01/01/1971-12/31/1971 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Personal Appointment Book, 12/27/1982-01/01/1984 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Appointments 1983, 01/01/1983-12/31/1983 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Appointments 1984, 01/01/1984-12/31/1984 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Appointments 1985, 01/01/1985-12/31/1985 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Appointment Book, 12/30/1985-01/04/1987 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Articles of Incorporation - Communications Satellite Corporation, 05/05/1969 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Audit Report Responses - Audit Report Finances, 04/07/1982-03/12/1985 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Bank of America International Limited, 10/20/1982-11/05/1982 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Board of Directors' Meetings June - December 1983, 06/08/1983-02/06/1984 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Board of Directors' Meetings January - June 1984, 12/29/1983-06/22/1984 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Board of Directors' Meetings July - December 1984, 07/16/1984-12/21/1984 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Broadcasting - August 6, 1979 Magazine Articles, 08/06/1979 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Broadcasting - December 3, 1979 Magazine Articles, 12/03/1979 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Broadcasting - September 15, 1980, 09/15/1980-10/02/1980 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Broadcasting - February 22, 1982, 02/22/1982 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Booz Allen Report [1/2], 07/1970-09/16/1970 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Booz Allen Report [2/2], 06/16/1970-10/22/1970 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Business Review - Week Ending 5/23/1980, 05/23/1980 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Briefing Book - Visit to Alpha Facilities July 29-30, 1981, 07/29/1981-07/30/1981 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - By-Laws of Communications Satellite Corporation, 03/19/1965-01/17/1969 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Cable Funding Corporation [1/4], 05/17/1972-06/28/1972 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Cable Funding Corporation [2/4], 06/16/1972 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Cable Funding Corporation [3/4], 08/22/1972-05/21/1976 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Cable Funding Corporation [4/4], 05/19/1972-05/01/1973 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Cable Funding Suit [1/3], 06/01/1976-11/21/1972 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Cable Funding Suit [2/3], 03/02/1973-12/27/1974 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Cable Funding Suit [3/3], 05/14/1973-02/05/1975 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Canda - Europe 1963, 05/18/1963-06/05/1963 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Charles A. Lindbergh Memorial Fund, 10/20/1976-10/25/1976 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Chester Burger & Co., Inc., 08/1982 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - China [1/3], 11/29/1978-04/24/1980 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - China [2/3], 1977-1980 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - China [3/3], 10/26/1976-01/11/1977 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Chron [Chronological] File 1965, 07/17/1964-01/24/1967 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Chron [Chronological] File 1967 [1/2], 07/17/1967-12/07/1967 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Chron [Chronological] File 1967 [2/2], 12/23/1966-07/11/1967 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Chron [Chronological] File 1968 [1/2], 07/10/1968-12/30/1968 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Chron [Chronological] File 1968 [2/2], 01/04/1968-06/19/1968 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Chron [Chronological] File 1969 [1/3], 10/02/1969-12/18/1969 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Chron [Chronological] File 1969 [2/3], 09/29/1969-05/28/1969 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Chron [Chronological] File 1969 [3/3], 05/09/1969-02/04/1969 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Chron [Chronological] File 1970 [1/2], 08/06/1970-12/29/1970 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Chron [Chronological] File 1970 [2/2], 01/02/1970-08/05/1970 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Chron [Chronological] File 1971 [1/2], 08/18/1971-12/22/1971 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Chron [Chronological] File 1971 [2/2], 01/04/1971-08/13/1971 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Chron [Chronological] File 1972 [1/2], 07/06/1972-12/29/1972 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Chron [Chronological] File 1972 [2/2], 01/04/1972-06/27/1972 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Chron [Chronological] File 1973 [2/2], 06/21/1973-12/13/1973 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Chron [Chronological] File 1973 [2/2], 01/08/1973-06/20/1973 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Chron [Chronological] File 1974 [1/2], 09/24/1974-12/03/1974 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Chron [Chronological] File 1974 [2/2], 01/04/1974-09/19/1974 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Chron [Chronological] File 1975 [1/2], 06/01/1975-12/25/1975 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Chron [Chronological] File 1975 [2/2], 01/09/1975-06/30/1975 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Chron [Chronological] File Jan. - June 1976, 01/06/1976-06/14/1976 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Chron [Chronological] File July 1976, 07/06/1976-07/29/1976 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Chron [Chronological] File 1976, 08/03/1976-08/27/1976 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Chron [Chronological] File Sept/Oct 1976, 09/08/1976-10/29/1976 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Chron [Chronologicl] File Nov/Dec 1976, 11/02/1976-12/25/1976 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Chron [Chronological] File Jan/Feb/March 1977, 01/07/1977-03/30/1977 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Chron [Chronological] File April/May 1977, 04/01/1977-05/27/1977 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Chron [Chronological] File June/July 1977 [1/2], 07/13/1977-07/27/1977 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Chron [Chronological] File June/July 1977 [1/2], 06/03/1977-07/12/1977 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Chron [Chronological] File Aug/Sept 1977 [1/2], 09/07/1977-09/30/1977 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Chron [Chronological] File Aug/Spet 1977 [1/2], 08/09/1977-09/02/1977 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Chron [Chronological] File Oct/Nov/Dec 1977 [1/2], 11/17/1977-12/30/1977 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Chron [Chronological] File Ovt/Nov/Dec 1977 [1/2], 10/03/1977-11/16/1977 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Chron [Chronological] File Jan/Feb 1978, 01/17/1978-02/28/1978 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Chron [Chronological] File March/April 1978, 03/03/1978-04/24/1978 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Chron [Chronological] File May/June 1978, 05/01/1978-06/30/1978 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Chron [Chronological] File July/Aug 1978, 07/19/1978-08/30/1978 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Chron [Chronological] File Sept/Oct 1978, 08/01/1978-10/31/1978 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Chron [Chronological] File Nov 1978, 11/01/1978-11/29/1978 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Chron [Chronological] File Dec 1978, 12/01/1978-12/29/1978 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Chron [Chronological] File Jan 1979, 01/02/1979-01/31/1979 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Chron [Chronological] File Feb 1979, 02/02/1979-02/28/1979 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Chron [Chronological] File March 1979 [1/2], 03/21/1979-03/27/1979 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Chron [Chronological] File March 1979 [2/2], 03/01/1979-03/20/1979 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Chron [Chronological] File April 1979, 04/30/1979-04/30/1979 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Chron [Chronolgical] File May 1979, 05/01/1979-05/31/1979 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Chron [Chronologial] File June 1979, 06/01/1979-06/29/1979 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Chron [Chronological] File July 1979, 07/05/1979-07/30/1979 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Chron [Chronological] File Aug 1979, 08/02/1979-08/29/1979 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Chron [Chronological] File Sept, 09/04/1979-09/28/1979 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Chron [Chronological] File Oct 1979, 10/01/1979-10/31/1979 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Chron [Chronological] File Nov 1979, 11/01/1979-11/30/1979 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Chron [Chronological] File Dec 1979, 12/04/1979-12/21/1979 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Chron [Chronological] File Jan 1980, 01/02/1980-01/29/1980 (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Chron [Chronological] File Feb 1980, 02/05/1980-02/28/1980 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Chron [Chronological] File March 1980, 03/07/1980-03/31/1980 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Chron [Chronological] File April 1980, 04/07/1980-04/29/1980 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Chron [Chronological] File May 1980 [1/2], 05/19/1980-05/30/1980 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Chron [Chronological] File May 1980 [2/2], 05/01/1980-05/14/1980 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Chron [Chronological] File June 1980, 06/02/1980-06/30/1980 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Chron [Chronological] File July 1980, 07/01/1980-07/30/1980 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Chron [Chronological] File aug 1980, 08/01/1980-08/29/1980 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Chron [Chronological] File Sept 1980, 09/02/1980-09/26/1980 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Chron [Chronological] File Oct 1980, 10/01/1980-10/31/1980 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Chron [Chronological] File Nov 1980, 11/03/1980-11/26/1980 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Chron [Chronological] File Dec 1980, 12/01/1980-12/23/1980 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Chron [Chronological] File Jan 1981, 01/1981 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Chron [Chronological] File Feb 1981, 02/02/1981-02/27/1981 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Chron [Chronological] File March 1981, 03/02/1981-03/25/1981 (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - Chron [Chronological] File April 1981, 04/02/1981-04/30/1981 (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Chron [Chronological] File May 1981, 05/04/1981-05/27/1981 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Chron [Chronological] File June 1981, 06/01/1981-06/30/1981 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Chron [Chronological] File July 1981, 07/09/1981-07/24/1981 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Chron [Chronological] File Aug 1981, 08/03/1981-08/31/1981 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Chron [Chronological] File Sept 1981, 09/03/1981-09/30/1981 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Chron [Chronological] File Oct 1981, 10/01/1981-10/30/1981 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Chron [Chronological] File Nov 1981, 11/04/1981-11/23/1981 (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Chron [Chronological] File, 12/02/1981-12/30/1981 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - Chron [Chronological] File Jan 1982, 01/05/1982-01/29/1982 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Chron [Chronological] File, 02/01/1982-02/26/1982 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Chron [Chronological] File March 1982, 03/01/1982-03/29/1982 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Chron [Chronological] File April 1982, 04/15/1982-04/30/1982 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Chron [Chronological] File May 1982, 05/03/1982-05/13/1982 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Chron [Chronological] File June 1982, 06/07/1982-06/30/1982 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Chron [Chronological] File July 1982, 07/01/1982-07/29/1982 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Chron [Chronological] File Aug 1982, 08/03/1982-08/26/1982 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Chron [Chronological] File Sept 1982, 09/02/1982-09/20/1982 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Chron [Chronological] Oct 1982, 10/02/1982-10/20/1982 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Chron [Chronological] File Nov 1982, 11/02/1982-11/30/1982 (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Chron [Chronological] File Dec 1982, 12/01/1982-12/30/1982 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Chron [Chronological] File Jan - March 1983, 01/07/1983-03/29/1983 (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - Chron [Chronological] File Arpil - Dec 1983, 04/06/1983-12/29/1983 (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - Chron [Chronological] File Jan - May 1984, 01/23/1984-05/29/1984 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Chron [Chronological] File June - Dec 1984, 06/04/1984-12/05/1984 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Chron [Chronological] File Jan 1985, 01/07/1985-02/21/1985 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Chron [Chronological] File April 1985, 04/01/1985-07/26/1985 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Citizens' Committee to Safeguard America (ABM) [1/2], 08/06/1970-08/31/1970 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Citizens' Committtee to Safeguard America (ABM)[2/2], 04/15/1970-06/25/1970 (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Civilian Space Policy and Applications -- Office of Technology Assessment (OTA), undated (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - Clarksburg vs L'Enfant, 10/13/1976-04/11/1977 (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - CM2, Inc., 10/06/1976-01/26/1977 (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - Commemorative Stamps, 12/08/1978-01/12/1982 (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Committee on Public Engineering Policy (COPEC), 03/1973-06/01/1973 (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Communications Satellite Journal of Spacecraft and Rockets Vol. 14 No. 7, July 1977, 07/1977-04/14/1978 (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Computer Working Committee, 06/26/1979-07/18/1980 (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Communications Satellite Corporation 1968 Revised Budget (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - COMSAT Board of Directors, 03/02/1984 (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - COMSAT Board of Directors' Meetings 1985, 01/02/1985-10/02/1985 (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - COMSAT European Trip Oct 25 - Nov 1982 -- Promotion and Advertising [1/2], 07/13/1982-08/09/1982 (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - COMSAT European Trip Oct 25 - Nov 5, 1982 -- Promotion and Advertising [2/2], 09/15/1982-10/26/1982 (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - COMSAT General Corp [1/2], 01/08/1974-04/22/1976 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - COMSAT General Corp. [2/2], 01/30/1973-11/14/1973 (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - COMSAT Government Documents, 08/31/1962-10/1971 (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - COMSAT Organization [1/2], 01/21/1971-09/17/1985 (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - COMSAT Organization [2/2], 11/04/1975-11/21/1983 (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - COMSAT Slides, undated (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - COMSAT Strategic Business Plan 1984 - 1985, 03/21/1984 (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - CTR Editorial Board (COMSAT Technical Review), 02/27/1981-04/30/1982 (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - Condolences S.H. Reiger, 07/15/1970-07/22/1970 (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - Conflicts of Interest, 01/28/1981-03/10/1981 (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Conflicts of Interest Program 1981, 06/30/1980-07/03/1984 (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - CONTEL [1/2], 1985-09/25/1986 (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - CONTEL [2/2], 03/06/1984-09/26/1986 (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Corporate Contribution 1982 [2/2], 04/30/1982-12/23/1982 (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - Coporate Contributions 1982 [2/2], 02/08/1982-08/11/1982 (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - Corporate Contributions 1983, 01/08/1983-02/03/1984 (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - DSB Administrative, 02/03/1971-09/12/1974 (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - Daily Log 1963, 04/01/1963-12/31/1963 (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - Daily Log 1964 [1/2], 06/10/1964-12/17/1964 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Daily Log 1964 [2/2], 01/02/1964-06/09/1964 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - Daily Log 1965 [1/2], 05/21/1965-12/30/1965 (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Daily Log 1965 [2/2], 01/04/1965-05/20/1965 (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - Daily Log 1966 [1/2], 05/03/1966-12/30/1966 (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - Daily Log 1966 [2/2], 01/03/1966-05/27/1966 (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Daily Log 1967 [1/2], 06/16/1967-12/29/1967 (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - Daily Log 1967 [2/2], 01/03/1967-06/15/1967 (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - Daily Log 1968 [1/2], 06/20/1968-12/31/1968 (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - Daily Log 1968 [2/2], 01/02/1968-06/19/1968 (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - Daily Log 1969 [1/2], 06/04/1969-12/31/1969 (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - Daily Log 1969 [2/2], 01/06/1969-06/03/1969 (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - Daily Log 1970 [1/2], 06/10/1970-12/31/1970 (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - Daily Log 1970 [2/2], 01/02/1970-06/09/1970 (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - Daily Log 1971 [1/2], 05/20/1971-12/30/1971 (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - Daily Log 1971 [2/2], 01/04/1971-05/18/1971 (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - Daily Log 1972 [1/2], 05/18/1972-12/29/1972 (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - Daily Log 1972 [2/2], 01/03/1972-05/16/1972 (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - Daily Log 1973 [1/2], 06/07/1973-12/21/1973 (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - Daily Log 1973 [2/2], 01/02/1973-06/06/1973 (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - Daily Log 1974 [1/2], 06/07/1974-12/24/1974 (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - Daily Log 1974 [2/2], 01/02/1974-06/06/1974 (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - Daily Log 1975 [1/2], 06/04/1975-12/24/1975 (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - Daily Log 1975 [2/2], 01/03/1975-06/03/1975 (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - Daily Log 1976 [1/2], 07/23/1976-12/16/1976 (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - Daily Log 1976 [2/2], 01/05/1976-07/22/1976 (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - Daily Log 1977, 01/04/1977-05/24/1977 (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - Daily Log Jan - June 1980, 01/03/1980-03/26/1980 (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - Defense Communications Agency CDCA, 10/26/1965-09/06/1966 (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - Definitive Arrangements 1970 - 1972, 05/12/1970-08/21/1972 (Box 30, Folder 7)
  - The Diebold Automated Office Program, 07/19/1979-11/02/1981 (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - Director General Selection Process - 1982 INTELSAT [1/2], 12/09/1982-12/30/1982 (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - Director General Selection Process - 1982 INTELSAT [2/2], 08/26/1982-12/08/1982 (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - Director General Selection Process - 1983 INTELSAT [1/2], 01/03/1983-03/09/1983 (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - Director General Selecation Process - 1983 INTELSAT [2/2], 03/31/1983-09/12/1983 (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - Domestic System -- Financial Forecasts 1970 - 1974 Opportunities Assessment Gp Rpt, 09/04/1968-07/03/1974 (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - Domestic System II 1970 - 1972 [1/2], 02/09/1971-07/07/1972 (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - Domestic System II 1970 - 1972 [2/2], 10/19/1970-01/29/1971 (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - Early Entry Program, 01/07/1982 (Box 32, Folder 2)
  - ERT Presentation to the Board Dec 1978, 12/1978 (Box 32, Folder 3)
  - ESOC (Earth Stations) [1/2], 08/26/1971-03/14/1973 (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - ESOC (Earth Stations) [2/2], 03/23/1967-12/31/1970 (Box 32, Folder 5)
  - Earth Station 1979 - 1981, 01/24/1979-06/03/1981 (Box 32, Folder 6)
  - Economic Club of Chicago -- Dec 3, 1964, 08/25/1964-12/17/1964 (Box 32, Folder 7)
  - Electronic Mail, 10/04/1976-10/26/1976 (Box 33, Folder 1)
  - Employees - COMSAT Board of Directors' Addresses, 02/02/1981-01/28/1983 (Box 33, Folder 2)
  - Employees - COMSAT General Business Communications, Inc. Addresses, 02/20/1981 (Box 33, Folder 3)
  - Employees - COMSAT General Corporation Addresses, 08/09/1980-02/20/1981 (Box 33, Folder 4)
  - Employees - COMSAT General Integrated Systems, Inc. Addresses, 03/25/1981 (Box 33, Folder 5)
  - Employees - COMSAT General Telesystems, Inc. Addresses, 01/22/1981-03/02/1981 (Box 33, Folder 6)
  - Employees - COMSAT Key Executives Addresses, undated (Box 33, Folder 7)
  - Employees - COMSAT Officers Addresses, 02/20/1981 (Box 33, Folder 8)
  - Employees - COMSAT World System Division Addresses, 03/02/1981 (Box 33, Folder 9)
  - Employees - Environmental Research & Technology, Inc. Addresses, 08/04/1980-04/03/1980 (Box 33, Folder 10)
  - Employees - INMARSAT Addresses, 11/15/1982 (Box 33, Folder 11)
  - Employees - INTELSAT, 12/1981 (Box 33, Folder 12)
  - Employees - Satellite Business Systems Addresses, 06/30/1980 (Box 33, Folder 13)
  - Employees - Satellite Television Corporation Addresses, 03/26/1981-12/01/1989 (Box 33, Folder 14)
  - ESOP, 08/26/1976-10/29/1976 (Box 33, Folder 15)
  - Europe Trip March 12 - 16, 1972, 02/28/1972 (Box 33, Folder 16)
  - Europe Trip June 16 - July 9, 1972, 10/13/1971-06/26/1972 (Box 33, Folder 17)
  - Exhibits - Public Affairs, Corporate Affairs, 07/07/1981-12/13/1982 (Box 33, Folder 18)